

SÉRGIO BUENO

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER





A Brazilian Software Engineer with 8+ years of experience, I'm capable to drive throughout the entire software life cycle, from requirement analysis to production support, including coding standards, reviews, source control management, build processes, testing, deploying, and managing distributed applications on popular cloud vendor's 'platforms.

CONTACT

+356 7706 1543



sergiocbueno@gmail.com



www.sergiobueno.me



San Gwann, Malta

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree Computer Engineering

PONTIFICAL CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY OF CAMPINAS 2011-2017

LANGUAGE

Portuguese

English

Spanish

Germany



WORK EXPERIENCE

CYKLPOINT LTD.

OCTOBER 2020 - PRESENT

Oct 2020 - Present **Lead Software Engineer**

BIT8 LTD.

APRIL 2019 - OCTOBER 2020

Development Team Lead Jan 2020 - Oct 2020 **Software Development Executive** Apr 2019 - Jan 2020

CI&T SOFTWARE S/A

FEBRUARY 2014 - MARCH 2019

Software Engineer

Global Coca-Cola Project May 2018 - Mar 2019 Modular Mining Inc. Project May 2017 - May 2018

Junior Software Engineer

Feb 2016 - May 2017 Coca-Cola Brazil Project

Intern Software Engineer

TransCanada Project Feb 2014 - Feb 2016

SKILLS







LINUX

CI/CD



